Divyesh Reddy Ellasiri

Divyesh
0810 | In Divyesh Reddy | Hortfolio | In Divyesh Reddy | Hortfolio | In Divyesh
18217090335 | Divyesh Reddy | In Divyesh Reddy |

SUMMARY

Highly Motivated and dedicated Computer Science Student with a Strong academic background. Eager to apply the learnt software development skills acquired in 3 years of studies and contribute significantly to the cause. Seeking to apply my skills in a dynamic and challenging workspace

WORK EXPERIENCE

Data Analyst and Outreach Intern

Oct 2022 - Feb 2023

- Outreach and Data Anlayst at Outleap Technologies.
- Worked in developing and implementing user sentiment analysis and optimised data organisation techniques.

Campus Ambassador

Oct 2021 - Oct 2022

- Leap Scholar Representative at SRM University AP, PoC responsible for the MoU
- Helped in spreading the word of Leap Scholar in our college, built and maintained a Discord Server with around 1500+ active members.

PROJECTS

Sentiment Analysis of Product based reviews using transformers

Link to Demo

Understanding the User Demographics for Product based reviews. By processing and analyzing text data, it determines the emotional tone, classifying it as positive, negative, or neutral. Used Multiple Machine Learning Models and BERT transformer model to perform the task.

- Machine Learning, Deep Learning.

Metro Operations Optimization

Link to Demo

A Small Data Science self exploration Project that involves systematic process of enhancing the efficiency, reliability, and effectiveness of Metro services through various data-driven techniques and operational adjustments. Showcases how analyzing existing data can guide decisions in real-time scheduling adjustments.

- Machine Learning, Data Science.

EDUCATION

2021 - present Bachelor's Degree at SRM University-Amaravati (GPA: 8.5/10.0) 2019 - 2021 Higher Secondary at Narayana E-Techno School (Percentage: 92.6)

SKILLS

Programming Languages C++,HTML, SS, MySQL, JavaScript, Python, Java, Bash

Frameworks Django (Python), React.js (JavaScript), Node.js (JavaScript), Tailwind CSS

Data Science Tools normalise Excel, Power BI, Tableau